to compete against guys who are also in
this draft and you know considered the
best guys in the world stepping into
this league. You know like I said I
don't take anything for thing for
granted and I just try to leave my mark
wherever I go at.
>> Can you talk about your decision to stay
at Georgia uh and not go and transfer to
one of those other schools when you had
offers?
>> Yeah. Um unfortunately I was you know
with the agency and um my mom wasn't
really feeling their representation and
how they go about things. Luckily, I was
surrounded by great people who who have
my best interest, I'll say. And you
know, we kind of just talked about the
pros and the cons of everything in my
situation, you know, and you know, the
what if and what ends. And you know, you
can do this from Georgia State. You
know, you can set set the pay for
Georgia State and be the biggest guy to
come from there. And you know, I I wore
that on my sleeve and I knew who I was
and I I knew regardless of where I'm at,
you know, the NFL family. My mom was
like, you know, don't chase the money,
son. The money's going to come.
>> Yeah. There's not a lot of Georgia State
products in the NFL, but there's already
one here in Tampa in Ben
>> Big Ben.
>> What's it going to be like to reunite
with him and have familiar face when you
get here?
>> Yeah, definitely. I know he's, you know,
picked it up and he has been blessed to
make the opportunity of a 53 man roster.
So, you know, if I could soak up any
game just from an older guy, I know he
kind of, you know, probably going about
the right way to handle his business. If
I could soak up any knowledge from him,
definitely looking forward to that.
you've made a lot of catches of 20 plus
yards. Um, you know, giving your team an
opportunity to score very quickly, you
know. Um, just what what's that like for
you when you have the ability to just in
in a in a split second, you know, change
kind of the trajectory of a game, the
outcome of a game with one big play?
What's that like for you?
>> Yeah, man. I say my prep preparation
coming into the game, you know, I I try
those things. [clears throat] I practice
really hard. you know, you know, when
the opportunity comes, I feel like I
excel. You know, luckily, I've been
surround surrounded by great people who
who had my best interest, and you know,
my game was definitely not founded, and
they helped me polish polish my game.
>> Where did your contested catch ability
come from? How did you hone that?
>> Yeah, I'll say that that's a more so of,
you know, playing multi sports, playing
basketball a lot. I'm a big fan of
basketball and, you know, just being a
guy who goes up and get the ball as a
rebound. That's kind of how I think of,
you know, just a jump ball. I'll say,
>> as far as wide receivers in the NFL or
or older guys, who who are some of the
guys you study? Who are some of the guys
you watch that you maybe model your game
after?
>> I say T. Higgins, you know, George
Pickkins. Um, I like J Mo a lot. you
know, a lot of those big guys who can
move in and out their in and out their
breaks, you know, go get the ball at the
same time, maybe catch it at the line of
scrimmage and, you know, take it to the
house.
>> Ted, what are your thoughts on catching
the football next season from Baker
Mayfield,
>> man?
Man, I I I haven't took a a chance to
grasp that in yet. And you know, when I
get the opportunity to get there, you
know, I'm I'mma be plugged to him and
I'm and I'm gonna take, you know,
advantage of every opportunity I get.
>> You got Chris Godwin in the wide
receiver room, Mecha Ibuka, Jaylen
McMillan, some of those other guys. How
excited are you to kind of learn from
Chris Godwin and some of these other
guys have had success in the league,
especially someone like Acha Ibuka and T
Johnson who both had success early on as
rookies?
>> Yeah, man. coming into this thing, you
know, the best feedback I got were from
these coaches is, you know, stick to
that older guy who does the thing right
and and I was really big on, you know, I
want to come in and have immediate
success. So, you know, I'm I'm a
standard hip pocket, maybe be a little
annoying at the same time, but I know,
you know, these are probably great guys
in the room and they're great leaders
and and I look up look forward to
looking up to those guys and I know I
know that's going to help me, you know,
expand my game. back to the seed bowl.
What was really an opportunity for you
to face tougher competition? Like what
was the mentality that you needed to
have that allowed you to to success
because to have success? Because you
know some people they can get
overwhelmed in those moments and
sometimes they can kind of wilt under
that pressure, but for you it seemed
like you really flourished.
>> Yeah, man. I'll say I'm I'm big in my
Bible. You know, I took that morning and
I prayed that day before I even hit the
field and I knew everything was in God's
hands. you know, uh, you know, I I
prepare myself well for for those
moments and I've been through, you know,
situations, close game, tight games and,
you know, I know what it feels like to
lose and, um, so anything, you know, I
do, you know, I I do it to my best
ability and I know, you know, how to how
to go about things and I feel like if I
give my all, you know, I'm comfortable
with that.
>> What are some of your biggest strengths
and biggest things you're bringing to
this roster, do you think?
Yeah, I I feel like, you know, I'm a
true big body ex receiver, but I also
can play any anywhere on the field and
I'm dynamic. You know, I'm I'm a team
player at the same time. If you're
asking me to do any role or play any
position, I'm going to I'm going to step
in and, you know, do my part.
>> How are you celebrating the draft? Who
are you with today? And and how's it
gone for you?
>> Yeah, about 40 to 50 family members,
close friends that I grew up with. my
family, you know, I'm really big on my
family, my household, my grandma and
cousins and all. They're they're out
here and they're excited, man. More
maybe more excited than me.
>> Yeah. What was the reaction like when
you got the phone call?
>> Definitely considering your school's
history.
>> Yeah. Yeah, definitely. Before I even
picked up the phone, they already were
like pulling out the cameras. They're
running up like everybody just getting
ready and excited for the moment. Uh,
actually I already had got the call
before I even, you know, got the chance
to see it on TV. So they were already
causing havoc in in the Airbnb and the
party and all of that. They were they
were going crazy.
>> Ted, Ted, I'm actually Georgia State
class of 2018, so I'm excited to have
you come down here. Um,
>> okay.
>> You are not.
>> Hell yeah. You already know what it is,
man. Uh,
>> so you are the highest drafted player in
Georgia State football history. Now,
just to come from Georgia State, make
history like that, what does it mean to
you, especially a program that I know
showed you a lot of love the last couple
years?
>> Yeah, man. I give a shout out to, you
know, coach Dale McGee and and my
receiver, coach, coach Damian Craig,
also to Quan Marshall, my assistant
receiver, coach, man. They they they had
a plan for me and they told me how they
felt about me just coming there. They
were truth truthful from the beginning
and they saw the potential with me and
you know they stick stick with me every
day and glued to me whether it's words
or encouragements or words words I
needed to hear.
>> Ted, if you had a message for the Bucks
fans watching this right now, what would
it be?
>> Y'all got a dog. I'm telling you you
like I seen all these people saying
sleep or the drive, man. I'm I'm here
for a reason.
>> Awesome. Anything else?
>> All right. Congrats.
Thank you.